[
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_113",
        "question": "A 12-year-old female presents with hemorrhagic crusts on the lips and erosions of the oral, genital, and conjunctival mucosa for 2 days. <br>- According to the parents, there was a pneumonia outbreak at school. <br>- The patient also had a high fever and cough a week before the onset of cutaneous lesions. <br>- The parents deny any new medication and a history of allergies. <br>- The physical exam reveals no other skin findings.",
        "option1": "Erythema multiforme major",
        "option2": "Herpetic gingivostomatitis",
        "option3": "Mycoplasma pneumoniae-induced rash and mucositis",
        "option4": "Stevens-Johnson Syndrome",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "94%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_110",
        "question": "A 25-year-old male presents with 2 years of pruriginous erythematous plaques with silver scales on elbows, knees and buttocks. <br>- He says that his father is known for hand and back arthritis. <br>- He denies personal and family history of dermatology conditions and atopy. <br>- Physical exam reveals pitting on all 10 fingernails.",
        "option1": "Psoriasis vulgaris",
        "option2": "Seborrheic dermatitis",
        "option3": "Atopic dermatitis",
        "option4": "Lichen planus",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "44%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_106",
        "question": "A 34-year-old woman presents with scaly lesions on the palms and soles. <br>- Lesions have been present for about a month. <br>- She denies recent genital sores or history of sexually transmitted diseases. <br>- She denies any family history of similar lesions on the palms or soles. <br>- She denies exposure to arsenic or well water. <br>- She denies being pregnant. <br>- She is otherwise healthy aside from a recent bout of stomach flu which she thinks she got from a bad piece of chicken. <br>- Physical examination reveals discrete scaly papules on the palms and soles.",
        "option1": "Secondary syphilis",
        "option2": "Keratoderma climactericum",
        "option3": "Pustular psoriasis",
        "option4": "Keratoderma blenorrhagicum",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "58%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_100",
        "question": "A 54-year-old woman presents with 2 years of gradual hair thinning. <br>- She says that her mother also experienced hair thinning starting in her 50s. <br>- She denies scalp itch. <br>- She denies clumps of hair coming out in the shower or on her pillow. <br>- She denies any preceding stressful life events. <br>- She denies wearing her hair in tight braids. <br>- She denies loss of eyebrows or eyelashes. <br>- Physical examination reveals frontotemporal hair thinning without scarring.",
        "option1": "Alopecia areata",
        "option2": "Telogen effluvium",
        "option3": "Androgenetic alopecia",
        "option4": "Central centrifugal cicatricial alopecia",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "86%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_052",
        "question": "A healthy 12-month-old infant girl presents with a yellowish-orange papule on the right upper extremity. <br>- Her mother first noticed this lesion approximately 6 months earlier. <br>- It has never bled, ulcerated, or formed blisters. <br>- The infant does not scratch the lesion nor appears otherwise bothered by it. <br>- However, when the lesion is rubbed, it appears to swell and turn bright red. <br>- On physical examination, there is a soft, oval-shaped, yellowish papule with a peripheral rim of erythema on the right extensor forearm.",
        "option1": "Solitary mastocytoma",
        "option2": "Pseudomonas nail infection",
        "option3": "Epidermolysis bullosa",
        "option4": "Bullous arthropod bites",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "72%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_024",
        "question": "A 1-year-old boy presents with a single, L-shaped, yellow-orange hairless patch over the left preauricular skin. <br>- The patient’s mother notes that he has never grown hair in that location. <br>- The mother is concerned because the area used to be smooth, but seems to be changing. <br>- The patient has a history of prematurity and low birthweight but is otherwise healthy. <br>- The patient has no relevant social or family history.",
        "option1": "Epidermal nevus",
        "option2": "Syringocystadenoma papilliferum.",
        "option3": "Juvenile xanthogranuloma",
        "option4": "Nevus sebaceous",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "78%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_138",
        "question": "A 34-year-old woman presents with complaints of a severely itchy rash affecting both lower legs that developed three days ago after returning from camping six days ago. <br>- She reports during the camping trip they often hiked for several hours a day, and she wore shorts due to the humid, hot weather. <br>- When the rash began, it began as small red bumps that formed larger fluid filled bumps. <br>- She has tried over the counter cortisone that helps with the itch a little bit. <br>- She denies any new topical lotions, laundry detergents, or body washes. <br>-   Physical exam reveals multiple streaks of yellow vesicles on bright pink erythematous bases in a linear distribution on the bilateral lower extremities.",
        "option1": "Irritant contact dermatitis",
        "option2": "Poison ivy allergic contact dermatitis",
        "option3": "Nummular eczema",
        "option4": "Scabies",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "49%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_078",
        "question": "A 54-year-old woman with a history of depression presents to the clinic with a 1-year history of an intermittent rash. <br>- She was hospitalized for COVID-19 approximately 1 year ago and soon after developed a rash all over her body. <br>- The lesions persist for several days and have a burning sensation. <br>- The patient has no associated joint pain or other systemic symptoms. <br>- She tried antihistamines for the rash with no symptomatic relief. <br>- On examination, erythematous wheals are evident on her arms and legs as well as her back and abdomen.",
        "option1": "Urticarial vasculitis",
        "option2": "Photodermatitis",
        "option3": "Systemic lupus erythematosus",
        "option4": "Schnitzler syndrome",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_009",
        "question": "A 43-year-old African American woman presents to the clinic with irritative lesions in the folds of her abdomen and in her genital region as well as painful ulcers in her oral mucosa. <br>- The patient reports noticing some flaccid blisters in addition to the lesions she presents with. <br>- On examination, erythematous, vegetative lesions are found. <br>- She states that the affected areas are painful but not pruritic. <br>- She has a previous history of herpes simplex virus (HSV).",
        "option1": "Squamous cell carcinoma",
        "option2": "Proderma gangraneosum",
        "option3": "Bowen’s disease",
        "option4": "Pemphigus vegetans",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_118",
        "question": "A 22-year-old male presents with a follicular eruption that has been present for 2 weeks. <br>- He has a history of anorexia nervosa and alcoholism. <br>- There is no identifiable preceding incident related to the eruption. <br>- He denies a history of atopy, drug use, and new medications. <br>- A review of systems shows positive findings for joint pain and bleeding gums. <br>- Physical exam reveals ecchymosis and purpuric follicular papules with corkscrew-like hair on his legs and arms.",
        "option1": "Scurvy",
        "option2": "Chronic liver disease",
        "option3": "IgA vasculitis",
        "option4": "Thrombocytopenic purpura",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "62%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_083",
        "question": "A 33-year-old Black man presents to a dermatology clinic with a 5-month history of asymptomatic lesions on his arms and trunk. <br>- He is otherwise healthy with no personal or family history of skin disease. <br>- He has no history of fever, cough, shortness of breath, or joint pain. <br>- The patient has not tried any treatments for these lesions. <br>- On examination, there are several smooth, well-demarcated hypopigmented plaques on his upper arms and left flank. <br>- He has no similar lesions elsewhere on his body.",
        "option1": "Rosacea",
        "option2": "Cutaneous sarcoidosis",
        "option3": "Cutaneous lupus",
        "option4": "Fungal infection",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "94%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_036",
        "question": "A 61-year-old woman presents concerned about a white discoloration on her left breast that she first noticed 6 months earlier. <br>- It itches at times, and she is worried it might be cancerous. <br>- She showed it to her gynecologist at her annual visit, and he referred her to the dermatology clinic. <br>- Physical examination of the left breast reveals a 10-cm white, smooth, porcelain-like plaque. <br>- There is no associated erythema and no noticeable scale.",
        "option1": "Tinea versicolor",
        "option2": "Vitiligo",
        "option3": "Lichen nitidus",
        "option4": "Lichen sclerosus et atrophicus",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_133",
        "question": "A 24-year-old obese woman presents to the dermatology clinic with darkening, rough skin around the neck for six months. <br>- The rash is not painful or itchy. <br>- She has tried to clean the area with over the counter shampoo and rubbing alcohol without improvement. <br>- She denies any rash elsewhere on the body. <br>- The rash always begins as dark patches, and she denies any blistering or redness before the dark spots develop. <br>-   Physical examination reveals thick, velvety ropey hyperpigmented rough, poorly demarcated plaques circumferentially around the neck.",
        "option1": "Acrochordon",
        "option2": "Confluent and reticulated papillomatosis  ",
        "option3": "Acanthosis nigricans",
        "option4": "Tinea versicolor",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "56%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_074",
        "question": "A 47-year-old otherwise healthy woman presents to the clinic with several concerns. <br>- Over the past several months, she has experienced thickening of her skin around her hands, forearms, and face. <br>- Her fingers turn blue and then pale when she is exposed to cold. <br>- Additional recent symptoms include fatigue and gastroesophageal reflux. <br>- She takes no medications and has no family history of autoimmune disease. <br>- On physical examination, the patient has skin thickening on the hands, forearms, and face. <br>- She also has hypopigmented macules on the hands and lower legs.",
        "option1": "Stiff-skin syndrome",
        "option2": "Systemic sclerosis",
        "option3": "Morphea",
        "option4": "Scleredema",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "94%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_064",
        "question": "A man, aged 68 years, with no known history of atopy presents with a 4-month history of an itchy and burning rash on the legs that has been recurring every winter for the past 3 years. <br>- He notes that he had dry skin at baseline and did not use emollients, but he did try hydrocortisone 1% cream without improvement. <br>- Examination revealed ovoid, erythematous, well-marginated plaques on the lower legs and dorsal feet with variable scaling and focal weeping and crusting. <br>- There were no nail changes, and the rest of his skin examination was notable only for xerosis.",
        "option1": "Psoriasis",
        "option2": "Bullous impetigo",
        "option3": "Nummular dermatitis",
        "option4": "Tinea corporis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "48%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    }
]